{"data":{"allMarkdownRemark":{"edges":[{"node":{"frontmatter":{"question":"Another question?","answer":null,"target_audience":["VISITOR"],"pageId":"93e034b0-a45e-4949-b0e5-a5bd1742b4d6"}}},{"node":{"frontmatter":{"question":"Can I save a CMS entry as draft?","answer":"Yes. On top of each CMS entry you might enable / disable draft status via provided toggle element. (Published entries will then be visible only inside the CMS of the digital hub and not on the public interface. ","target_audience":["PROFESSIONAL"],"pageId":"7c290917-922e-4ac6-ab16-e29f9a31f959"}}},{"node":{"frontmatter":{"question":"Can I share my new entry on the DigitalHub on social media?","answer":"..still to answer","target_audience":["VISITOR"],"pageId":"c4cd2547-58f1-47dc-adb4-1d8cbbeafbb2"}}},{"node":{"frontmatter":{"question":"Demo","answer":"This is a demo","target_audience":["VISITOR"],"pageId":"8b43785f-774b-40f2-9dc7-964c72bf1633"}}},{"node":{"frontmatter":{"question":"How can I directly contact a person/institution via personal messages in the chat?","answer":"....lets see","target_audience":["VISITOR"],"pageId":"8720c44b-e274-4d62-9d1d-7f507f086870"}}},{"node":{"frontmatter":{"question":"How can I join the Reinherit Forum? ","answer":"If you want to contribute to the Reinherit Forum you either need a github account, a gitlab account or log in with your Twitter credentials. ","target_audience":["VISITOR","PROFESSIONAL"],"pageId":"e650e4dd-b929-4f96-bddb-d1305ad9de41"}}},{"node":{"frontmatter":{"question":"How long does it take till my new entries are visible?","answer":"still to answer","target_audience":["VISITOR"],"pageId":"14f0c4a1-b30d-4e12-896e-e48c80c562dd"}}},{"node":{"frontmatter":{"question":"How to create an account?","answer":"now","target_audience":["VISITOR"],"pageId":"b8181ff8-f05a-46c5-8cb1-e13cd4f3f9dc"}}},{"node":{"frontmatter":{"question":"How to debug my markdown page?","answer":null,"target_audience":["VISITOR"],"pageId":"12f791b2-edec-4be9-ab2f-213a12b6d525"}}},{"node":{"frontmatter":{"question":"I am a cultural heritage professional and would like to add interesting content to the Hub. How can I do that?","answer":"If you want to add content to the hub, please do so via the forms we provided. With this forms you can either show case your institution, promote an upcoming event or write a blogentry on a certain theme. Please keep in mind - especially when promoting an event -  that it will take some time before your submitted content will be reviewed and published.   ","target_audience":["PROFESSIONAL"],"pageId":"68287848-8a07-4add-baf7-fd3b8c2f06b5"}}},{"node":{"frontmatter":{"question":"I canÂ´t see my new entry in the CMS","answer":"Refresh the page F5.","target_audience":["VISITOR","PROFESSIONAL"],"pageId":"ea5aeace-94f9-41c1-b46e-40de8009e834"}}},{"node":{"frontmatter":{"question":"The image upload in the CMS didn't work, what went wrong?","answer":"Maybe your image is bigger than the set limit for image uploads, which is 100kb per image. If so you can either resize the image (a Manual on how to do so can be found under Manuals), or consider hosting the image yourself (e.g. via google drive) and link it to the hub. ","target_audience":["PROFESSIONAL"],"pageId":"63b4098a-938d-468c-8b23-8e6b2def8d08"}}},{"node":{"frontmatter":{"question":"What is a CMS?","answer":"CMS, a Content Management System, is used for easy content creation on a website without requiring special technical or programming knowledge. A well known example is WordPress. For more information see: https://kinsta.com/knowledgebase/content-management-system/","target_audience":["VISITOR"],"pageId":"923d8c07-fb72-4707-ae39-5be71c9cdbbd"}}},{"node":{"frontmatter":{"question":"What is the markdown mode?","answer":"still to answer","target_audience":["VISITOR","PROFESSIONAL"],"pageId":"e62410ba-78d4-4d5f-ba74-6dfc212b6143"}}},{"node":{"frontmatter":{"question":"Will there be a website maintenance after the project runtime? ","answer":"..open","target_audience":["VISITOR"],"pageId":"8a881bbf-c844-4fc7-a995-51359b62ed39"}}}]}}}